Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty (VADP); Records apap304
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Communication, 1981-2022; 4; 1.4 cubic ft.; 186 MB
  - McClung Proof Sign Off Sheet RMB for Letterhead, 2020 March 31
  - McClung Proof Sign Off Sheet RMB for Not Current Donors Letters & Reply Cards, 2020 March 31
  - McClung Proof Sign Off Sheet RMB for Not Donors Letters & Reply Cards, 2020 March 31
  - McClung Proof Sign Off Sheet RMB for Donation Reply Form, 2020 April 1
  - Draft Message on Insider Update Videos Calls, 2020 April 7
  - Draft Message on Insider Update Videos Calls, Revised, 2020 April 7
  - Draft Spring Fundraising Appeal Message, 2020 April 7
  - Draft Spring Fundraising Appeal Message, Revision, 2020 April 9
  - Draft Spring Fundraising Appeal Message, Second Revision, 2020 April 9
  - Insider Update Video Image, 2020 April 17
  - Letter to Helen Prejean About "Dead Run: the Shocking Story of Dennis Stockton and Life on Death Row in America" Book, 2020 May 7
  - Abolition University Session on National Movement, Revised Photo, 2020 May 19
  - Abolition University Session on National Movement Speaker Photo, 2020 May 19
  - Abolition University Session on Conservative Death Penalty Opposition Photo, 2020 May 28
  - VADP and Race, Second Draft, 2020 June 4
  - "Racial inequities in America's death penalty" by Kristina Leslie, Draft with MES Edits, 2020 June 5
  - "Racial inequities in America's death penalty" by Kristina Leslie, Edited to 750 words, 2020 June 5
  - VADP and Race, Third Draft, 2020 June 5
  - The Case for Death Penalty Abolition in Virginia, 2020 June 11
  - The Case for Death Penalty Abolition in Virginia, Revised, 2020 June 11
  - The Case for Death Penalty Abolition in Virginia, Final, 2020 June 12
  - Op-Ed "The Nation's Racism & Virginia's Death Penalty" by Kristina Leslie and Vivian Hernandez, Draft, 2020 June 19
  - Op-Ed "The Nation's Racism & Virginia's Death Penalty" by Kristina Leslie and Vivian Hernandez, Draft with MES and Paul Edits, 2020 June 20
  - Op-Ed "The Nation's Racism & Virginia's Death Penalty" by Kristina Leslie and Vivian Hernandez, Draft with MES Edits, 2020 June 20
  - Blue Views Article "Repeal Virginia's Death Penalty: All Black Lives Matter" by Paul O'Shea, MES Edits, 2020 July 1
  - Plea Bargain Myth, National Document from 8th Amendment Project, 2020 July 13
  - Plea Bargaining & the Death Penalty in Virginia, 2020 July 15
  - Death Penalty Informtion Center Death Penalty Fact Sheet, 2020 July 17
  - Op-Ed for Washington Post, Race and the Death Penalty by Paul O'Shea, 2020 July 23
  - Letter from Inmate to Kristina Leslie, 2020 August 10
  - Statement on Federal Executions, MES Edits, 2020 August 27
  - Award Luncheon Press Release, MES Edits, 2020 September 3
  - Blue Views Article "VADP Awards Luncheon Speakers Focus On Virginia Death Penalty Repeal in 2021" by Paul O'Shea, 2020 November 2
  - Op-Ed "Conservative Principles Call for Death Penalty Repeal", 2020 November 9
  - VADP Draft End of Year Appeal Email Blast, 2020 November 9
  - Zoom Account Pages, Instructions Image, 2020 November 9
  - Zoom Account Pages, Instructions Image 2, 2020 November 9
  - Virginia Interfaith Center for Public Policy Livestream "Abolish theDeath Penalty in Virginia" Event Flyer, 2020 November 12
  - VADP Annual Report Finance Info, 2020; 2021 February 25
  - VADP Annual Report, Outer Section, Version F, 2020; 2021 February 25
  - VADP Annual Report, Outer Section, Version G, 2020; 2021 March 1
  - VADP Annual Report, Outer Section, Version J, 2020; 2021 March 11
  - VADP Annual Report, Abolition History, Version N, 2020; 2021 March 12
  - VADP Annual Report, Abolition History, Version O, 2020; 2021 March 15
  - VADP Annual Report, Abolition History, Version P, Edits by Paul, 2020; 2021 March 16
  - VADP Annual Report, Abolition History, Version Q, 2020; 2021 March 16
  - VADP Annual Report, Final, 2020; 2021 March 17
  - VADP Annual Report, Final, 2020; 2021 March 17
  - VADP Annual Report, Final Revision, 2020; 2021 March 17
  - VADP Annual Report Cover, Final, 2020; 2021 May 27
  - Prosecutors Call for Death Penalty Abolition, Press Release, 2021 January 14
  - Photo of MES at RVA Prayer Vigil, 2021 January 22
  - Photo of RVA Prayer Vigil, 2021 January 22
  - Senate Floor Tally Photo, 2021 February 3
  - Board Viritual Toast to Abolition Photo, 2021 February 5
  - Facts and Ideas for Senator Kaine Op-Ed on Virginia Abolishing the Death Penalty, 2021 February 5
  - VADP Board Viritual Victory Gathering Photo, 2021 February 5
  - Book Proposal, History of Death Penalty Abolition in Virginia, 2021 February 16
  - Capital Defender Viritual Celebration Photo, 2021 February 18
  - Letter to PBS Asking them to Cover Virginia Abolishing the Death Penalty on NewsHour, 2021 February 18
  - Delegate Mike Mullin on Senate Abolition Bill Photo, 2021 February 22
  - Virginia Death Penalty Successful Abolition Press Release Draft 1, 2021 March 1
  - Death Penalty Successfully Abolished, Press Release, Second Draft, 2021 March 2; 2021 March 1
  - Book Proposal, The Story of Death Penalty Abolition in Virginia, 2021 March 3
  - "Group Shot 2" Photo, 2021 March 12
  - Statement at Death Penalty Abolition Bill Signing Ceremony by Jayne Barnard, VADP Vice-President, Big Print, 2021 March 24
  - Statement at Death Penalty Abolition Bill Signing Ceremony by Jayne Barnard, VADP Vice-President, Print Version, 2021 March 24
  - Statement at Death Penalty Abolition Bill Signing Ceremony by Jayne Barnard, VADP Vice-President, Version with Branding, 2021 March 24
  - Possible Locations to Exhibit Virginia's Electric Chair, 2021 March 30
  - Response to John Pike Regarding Candidates and the Death Penalty, 2021 August 18
  - Signed Book Cover Letter for Key Allies, 2022 May 20
  - Signed Book Cover Letter for Key Allies with Mailing Merges, 2022 May 20
  - Signed Book Cover Letter for Large Donors, 2022 May 20
  - Signed Book Cover Letter for Large Donors with Mailing Merges 1, 2022 May 20
  - Signed Book Cover Letter for Large Donors with Mailing Merges 2, 2022 May 20
  - VADP Return Address Labels, 2022 May 24
  - Form Letter for Attorney General Terry, Undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Letters to and from Joe Giarratano, Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Response - Prison Pen Pal Question, Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - The Exonerated Flyer, Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - VADP Crime Commission Letter, Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - VADP Mailings, Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Activities, 1990-2021; 5; 2.0 cubic ft.; 2.11 GB
  This series contains materials related to projects and programs hosted and or attended by Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty such as the National Weekend of Faith, National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (NCADP) Conferences, Starving for Justice, VADP Conferences, Virginia Catholic Conference, various regional meetings, Juvenile Death Penalty Awareness Day, fasts and vigils, and coalition meetings. It also contains activity planning documents for VADP.
  - 1000th Execution, 2002; 2005; Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 2002 National Weekend of Faith, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 2002 NCADP Conference (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 2003 National Weekend of Faith, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 2003 NCADP Conference (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 2003 Starving for Justice (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 2003 VADP Conference (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 2004 National Weekend of Faith, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 2004 NCADP Conference (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 2004 VADP Death Penalty Awareness Day (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 2004 VADP Fast and Vigil (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 2005 National Weekend of Faith (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 2005 VADP Conference (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 2005 Virginia Catholic Conference (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 2006 National Weekend of Faith, Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 2006 VADP Fast and Vigil (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 2007 Virginia Catholic Conference (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 2007 Virginia Cure Packet (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 2015 Activity Documents (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 2015 Lobbying Hours IRS Form 990, 2016 January 19
  - 2016 Activity Documents (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 2017 Activity Documents (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 2017 Lobbying Hours from IRS Form 990, 2018 February 1
  - 2018 Activity Documents (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 2019 Activity Documents (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 2020-2021 Activity Documents (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 21 Day Rule Project, 2003-2004; Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - A Day for All People of Faith, 2007; Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - ACLU Student DD Conference Packet, 2003; Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Activism Conference, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Alliance to End Juvenile Death Penalty, 2005; Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Amnesty International DP Packet - French, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Amnesty International Mid Atlantic Conference, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Bell Vigil Follow-Up Spreadsheet, 2009 July 14
  - Breaking the Cycle of Violence, Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Broken Justice, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Call for List, Richmond Regional Meeting, 2017 November 9
  - Call for List, Richmond Regional Meeting, Revised, 2017 November 9
  - Catholic Advocacy, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Centerville High School, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Charlottesville, P&J Gathering, VADP Remarks, 2015 June 9
  - Charlottesville, P&J Gathering, VADP Remarks, 2016 June 14
  - Charlottesville Regional Meeting Photos, 2015 April 22
  - Charlottesville Regional Meeting Photos, 2015 November 11
  - Charlottesville Regional Meeting RSVP List, 2017 May 16
  - Charlottesville Regional Meeting RSVP List, 2017 November 8
  - Christopher Scott Vigil, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - "Chville" Guests of Bill Wardle, 2020 October 22
  - "Chville" Guests of Bill Wardle, Spreadsheet, 2020 August 13
  - "Chville" Photo, 2016 April; 2016 May 24
  - "Chville" Photo, 2017 May; 2017 May 17
  - "Chville" Photo, Resized, 2017 May; 2018 October 11
  - "Chville" Photos, 2015 November; 2015 November 27
  - "Chville" Regional Meeting RSVP List, 2018 April 26
  - Clemency Petition for JT Jackson, 2011 August 12
  - Commonwealth Litigation Packet, 2004-2006; Undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Conservatives Concerned About the Death Penalty Display Table at YAL Conference, Dale and Hannach, 2018 July 31; 2018 November 13
  - Dale at VADP Display Table at VRFW Convention, 2018 May 8
  - Dale at VADP Display Table at VRFW Convention, Revised, 2018 May 8
  - Dale at VADP Display Table at VRFW Convention, Small, 2018 May 8
  - Dale at VFRW Convention, 2018 May 8
  - Dale, Hannach, and George at YAL Conference, 2018 July 31; 2018 November 13
  - Dale with Sister Helen Prejean in Hampton with VADP Table, 2018 November 13
  - Death Penalty Awareness Day, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Death Penalty Awareness Day, 2006; Undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Death Penalty in the US, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Death Penalty Issue Packet, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Death Penalty Press Conference Materials, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Death Penalty Talk by Shane Claiborne, Planning Notes, 2018 September 15
  - Death Penalty Talk by Shane Claiborne, Planning Notes, First Revision, 2019 February 16
  - Death Penalty Talk by Shane Claiborne, Planning Notes, Second Revision, 2019 February 16
  - Death Penalty Talk by Shane Claiborne, Planning Notes, Third Revision, 2019 February 16
  - Death Penalty Talk by Shane Clairborne, Schedule, 2019 February 16
  - Death Penalty Talk by Shane Clairborne, Schedule, 2019 February 16
  - Death Penalty Talk by Shane Clairborne, Stipend Letters to Joe & Linell, 2019 February 16; 2019 February 28
  - Declaration of Life, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Donors of over $250 to Receive Signed Copy of Virginia Death Penalty Book Plus Key Allies, 2022 May 19
  - Donors of over $250 to Receive Signed Copy of Virginia Death Penalty Book Plus Key Allies, 2022 May 19
  - Earl Washington Release Case, 2001; Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Eddie Bell Flyer, Version 1, 2009 February 18
  - Eddie Bell Flyer, Version 2, 2009 February 19
  - Execution Vigil, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Faith, Values and Capital Punishment In Virginia, 2005; Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - For Whom the Bell Tolls Project, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Fredericksburg Women VADP Signups, 2018 September 25
  - Freedom Information Advisory Council, 2001; Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Friends Committee and Commonwealth Legislation, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Home Page Slide for Regional Meeting, 2018; 2018 October 15
  - Image of Barter Theater Panel on Death Penalty, 2018 April 15
  - Image of Bon Air Severe Mental Illness Petitions Given to Senator Sturtevant, 2018 December 3
  - Image of Briley Execution Sign, 2021 March 12
  - Image of Bryan Stevenson at VCU, 2017 April 12
  - Image of "Chville" Execution Vigil, 2015 October 1
  - Image of "Chville" Regional Meeting, 2016 May 4
  - Image of "Chville" Regional Meeting, 2017 May 16
  - Image of "Chville" Regional Meeting, 2017 November 8
  - Image of "Chville" Regional Meeting, 2018 April 26
  - Image of Dale Brumfield Display Table Inside Scoop Promo, 2018 August; 2018 September 3
  - Image of Delegate Chris Hurst on Senate Abolition Bill, 2021 February 22
  - Image of Electric Chair with Guard, 1980; 2016 February 23
  - Image of Greensville Execution Vigil 1, 1990; 2021 March 11
  - Image of Greensville Execution Vigil 2, 1990; 2021 March 11
  - Image of Hampton Event with Sister Helen & Dale, 2018 October 30
  - Image of House Death Penalty Abolition Floor Vote, 2021 February 5
  - Image of Lynchburg Regional Meeting, 2017 May 4
  - Image of National American Bar Association Conference on Severe Mental Illness, 2016 December 6
  - Image of Norfolk Execution Vigil, 2017 July 6
  - Image of Norfolk Regional Meeting, 2015 October 21
  - Image of Norfolk Regional Meeting, 2016 April 28
  - Image of Norfolk Regional Meeting, 2016 October 25
  - Image of Norfolk Regional Meeting, 2017 October 24
  - Image of Norfolk Regional Meeting, 2018 May 2
  - Image of NoVa Regional Meeting, 2015 October 27
  - Image of NoVa Regional Meeting, 2016 November 10
  - Image of NoVa Regional Meeting, 2017 December 13
  - Image of NoVa Regional Meeting, 2018 April 19
  - Image of PH Libertarian VADP Signups, 2018 October 2
  - Image of Richmond Regional Meeting, 2017 May 11
  - Image of "RVA" Regional Meeting, 2017 November 9
  - Image of Senate Floor Vote on Severe Mental Illness, 2020 January 30
  - Image of Senate Judiciary Support Abolition, 2021 January 18
  - Image of Senate Pass House Death Penalty Bill, 2021 February 22
  - Image of Severe Mental Illness Senate Committee Debate, 2019 January 14
  - Image of Severe Mental Illness Senate Committee Debate, Small, 2019 January 14
  - Image of Severe Mental Illness Senate Floor Tally, 2019 January 17
  - Image of Severe Mental Illness Senate Floor Tally, Small, 2019 January 17
  - Image of Talk at Chatham Rotary, 2018 March 22
  - Image of Virginia Death Penalty Coalition Meeting on Zoom, 2021 March 9
  - Images of 2015 VADP Awards Luncheon, 2015 October 10
  - Images of 2016 VADP Awards Luncheon, 2016 October 8
  - Images of 2017 VADP Awards Luncheon, 2017 October 14
  - Images of 2018 VADP Awards Luncheon, 2019 March 24
  - Images of 2019 VADP Awards Luncheon, 2019 October 5
  - Images of 2020 VADP Awards Luncheon, 2020 October 24
  - Images of Abolition Bill Signing Ceremony, 2021 March 24
  - Images of All States Catholic Church Death Penalty Event, 2012 June 16; 2012 June 17
  - Images of Audience for Jerry Givens at University of Richmond, 2015 September 24
  - Images of Board Meeting, 2015 April 25
  - Images of Board Meeting, 2017 January 21
  - Images of Board Meeting, 2017 September 16
  - Images of Board Meeting, 2018 January 13
  - Images of Board Meeting, 2019 January 12
  - Images of Board Meeting, 2019 April 27
  - Images of "Chville" Death Penalty Talk, 2013 May 14
  - Images of "Chville" Event, 2015 June 9
  - Images of "Chville" Friend-Raiser, 2017 June 27
  - Images of "Chville" Regional Meeting, 2015 April 22
  - Images of Clergy Press Conference, 2016 April 18
  - Images of Cons "Friend-Raiser", 2018 May 14
  - Images of DC "Friend-Raiser", 2017 February 16
  - Images of Death Penalty Abolition Party, 2021 June 26
  - Images of Death Penalty Abolition Victory Dinner, 2021 November 20
  - Images of Death Penalty Abolition Victory Lunch, 2021 November 21
  - Images of Death Penalty Event at Olser & Bishop, 2012 October 7; 2012 October 8
  - Images of Death Penalty in Fredericksburg, 2017 January 22
  - Images of Death Penalty Panel at Saint Thomas Aquinas, 2012 January 22; 2012 June 17
  - Images of Death Penalty Talk at Mennonite Church, 2012 October 21
  - Images of Death Penalty Talk at St. Andrews Roanoke, 2016 October 15
  - Images of Donor Dinner, 2019 March 23
  - Images of ElderStudy Talk, 2017 October 14
  - Images of Event "Jesus on Trial", 2012 October 9; 2012 October 10
  - Images of Executions Meeting, 2016 January 6
  - Images of Greensville Vigil, 2021 March 11
  - Images of House Criminal Law Subcommittee Meeting, 2021 January 29
  - Images of Letter to Govenor Teleguz at Episocpal Church, 2017 April 10
  - Images of Loudon County Democrats Death Penalty Forum, 2017 November 14
  - Images of MLK Lobby Day, 2017 January 16
  - Images of Morva Vigil, 2017 July
  - Images of National Abolition Conference in New Orleans, 2015 October 1; 2015 September 30-2015 October 2
  - Images of Norfolk Regional Meeting, 2015 May 13
  - Images of NoVA Execution Vigil, 2015 October 1
  - Images of NoVA Regional Meeting, 2015 January 14
  - Images of NoVA Regional Meeting, 2016 May 11
  - Images of NoVA Regional Meeting, 2017 April 27
  - Images of Penitentiary Marker, 2017 February 24
  - Images of Prayer Vigil at Penitentiary Site, 2021 January 22
  - Images of Richmond Virginia Execution Vigil, 2017 July 6
  - Images of Roanoke Regional Meeting, 2015 May 26
  - Images of Roanoke Regional Meeting, 2016 October 13
  - Images of "SALT: Social Action Linking Together" Event, 2012 October 20
  - Images of SCOTUS Fast and Vigil, 2016 June 29
  - Images of SCOTUS Fast and Vigil, 2017 June 29
  - Images of Senate Floor Tally Vote, 2021 February 3
  - Images of Shane Death Penalty in "Chville", 2019 February 16
  - Images of Southern States Death Penalty Meeting, 2017 December 8
  - Images of St. James Episcopal Church, 2017 March 26
  - Images of Staff Retreat, 2013 May 10
  - Images of Suddes Board Training, 2016 October 28
  - Images of University of Virginia "Incarceration Nation", 2016 April 12
  - Images of VADP Board Meeting, 2016 April 9
  - Images of VADP Board Meeting, 2016 September 17
  - Images of Virginia Interfaith Center of Public Policy, 2016 December 15
  - Images of William and Mary Event, 2017 March 22
  - Images of Wittness to Innocence Event, 2011 June 11; 2015 May 10; 2011 July 29
  - Investigating Capital Cases Conference, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Juvenile Death Penalty Awareness Day- Press Conference Documents, 2005 January 17; 2005 January 18 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Juvenile Death Penalty Packet, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Juvenile DP Awareness Day Packet, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Listening Project - [RESTRICTED], 1993-1994; Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Must consult archivist before viewing this material.
  - Listening Project for Chris B. - [RESTRICTED], Undated (Video-tape 36)
  - Lynchburg Photo, 2017 April; 2017 May 5
  - Lynchburg Regional Meeting "First Christian Church" Room Reservation Form, 2017 May 4
  - Lynchburg Regional Meeting RSVP List, 2017 May 4
  - Montreal Death Penalty Conference, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Moratorium, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Moratorium Now Packet, 2004-2005; Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Muhammad and Malvo Trial Vigils, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Norfolk Photo, 2015 May; 2015 May 14
  - Norfolk Photo, 2016 October; 2016 October 27
  - Norfolk Photo, 2018 April
  - Norfolk Photo, Resized, 2018 April
  - Norfolk Regional Meeting Photo, 2015 May 13; 2015 July 21
  - Norfolk Regional Meeting, Photos, 2015 May 13; 2015 May 14
  - Norfolk Regional Meeting Photos, 2015 October 21
  - Norfolk Regional Meeting RSVP List, 2018 May 2
  - Norfolk Regional Meeting RSVP Meeting List, 2017 October 24
  - NoVa Meeting on Upcoming Executions, RSVP Lists, 2016 January 6
  - NoVa Photo, 2015 October; 2015 October 29
  - NoVa Photo, 2016 April; 2016 May 24
  - NoVa Photo, 2017 April; 2017 April 28
  - NoVA Photo, 2018 April
  - NoVa Photos, 2017 December
  - NoVA Regional Meeting Photos, 2015 April 13
  - NoVA Regional Meeting Photos, 2015 October 27
  - NoVa Regional Meeting Photos, 2017 April 27
  - NoVa Regional Meeting RSVP List, 2017 December 13
  - NoVA Regional Meeting RSVP List, 2018 April 19
  - October & November 2015, Regional VADP Meeting Remarks, 2015 October; 2015 November; 2015 October 19
  - People United, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Regional VADP Pot Luck Dinner Meeting Agenda, Charlottesville, 2011 February 20
  - Regional VADP Pot Luck Dinner Meeting Agenda, Norfolk, 2011 November 15
  - Regional VADP Pot Luck Dinner Meeting Agenda, Richmond, 2011 November 10
  - Religious Organization Against The Death Penalty, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Respect Life Packet, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Richmond Regional Meeting RSVP List, 2017 May 11
  - Roanoke Libertarian Meeting, VADP Signup Sheet, 2018 November 14
  - Roanoke Photo, 2015 May; 2015 May 27
  - Roanoke Photo, 2016 October; 2016 October 14
  - Roanoke Photo, Resized, 2015 May; 2018 September 25
  - Roanoke Regional Meeting Photo, 2015 May 26; 2015 July 24
  - Roanoke Regional Meeting Photo, Resized, 2015 May 26; 2015 July 21
  - Roanoke Regional Meeting Photos, 2015 May 26; 2015 June 1
  - Robin Lovitt Vigil, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - "RVA" Photo, 2017 May; 2017 May 13
  - "RVA" Photo, 2017 November; 2017 November 10
  - "RVA" Photo, Resized, 2017 May; 2018 October 11
  - "RVA" Regional Meeting RSVP List, 2018 April 10
  - SCOTUS Fast & Vigil Photo, Resized, 2017; 2018 June 20
  - Steve Northup, Diann Rust Tierney, and Jerry Givens Photo, 2011 July 29
  - Summit to Strategize for Abolition, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - The Moratorium Campaign, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Tidewater JustFaith Graduation Flyer, 2015 May 14; 2015 May 5
  - Tom Petersik, Poor Quality Image, 2019 July 18
  - VA Electric Chair Video Screenshots, 2016 March 10
  - VADP Annual Conference, 2000 October 14 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - VADP Fast and Vigil, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - VADP Legislative Survey, 2004-2005; Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - VADP Martin Luther King Jr., 2007; Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - VADP Table Display, Family Peace Festival, 2011 October; 2020 October 21
  - VADP Victory Celebration, 2021 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - VADP Write-A-Thon, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Vigil for Walter Cole and James Hudson, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Vigil Program for Gleason, 2013 January 14
  - Vigil Program for Jackson, 2011 August 10
  - Virginia CURE, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Execution Vigil, Charlottesville Photos, 2015 October 1
  - Virginia Execution Vigil, Greensville Photos, 2017 July 6
  - Virginia Execution Vigil, NoVA Photos, 2017 January 18
  - Virginia Friends Advocacy Day, 2005; Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Virginia General Assembly Catholic Advocacy Day, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Virginia General Assembly Day for People of Faith, 2003-2004; Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Virginia General Assembly Death Penalty Awareness Day, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Virginia General Assembly Interfaith Advocacy Day, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Virginia General Assembly Jewish Advocacy Day, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Virginia House Representatives Survey, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Virginia Journey of Hope, 2006; Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)